Presenter: OK. It begins with B.
It’s an adjective for a man who has no hair on his head!
Right.
It begins with C.
It’s an adjective.
It describes a place where there are a lot of people, for example a restaurant or a beach in the summer.
Right.
It begins with G.
They’re things which people wear on their hands.
Right.
It begins with K.
It’s the room where people cook.
Right.
It begins with L.
It’s an adjective for someone who doesn’t like studying or working, for example.
It’s the opposite of hard-working.
Right.
It begins with T.
It’s a thing which you use in an airport to help you with your cases, or in a
supermarket to put your shopping in…
Just three seconds left…